Junior in Love!
Problem Child 3 is a comedy, family, tv movie film directed by Greg Beeman.
Now a pre-teen, Junior has fallen head over heels for a classmate who doesn't even notice him, but does notice
three other boys – a child star, a hockey player and a Boy Scout – who are rivals to Junior.
This means war!
Ben Healy, played by William Katt.
Junior Healy, played by Justin Chapman.
Scoutmaster Phlim, played by Sherman Howard.
Dr. Gray, played by Carolyn Lowery.
Murph / Bertha, played by Eric Edwards.
Corky, played by Blake McIver Ewing.
Problem Child is a 1990 American comedy film directed by Dennis Dugan in his
feature film directorial debut and produced by Robert Simonds.
The film stars John Ritter, Michael Oliver, Jack Warden, Gilbert
Gottfried, Amy Yasbeck, and Michael Richards.
The film revolves around a man named Ben (Ritter), who, after learning his
wife is infertile, decides to adopt a boy named Junior (Oliver).
Unbeknownst to him, Junior is a disruptive and unruly
child, who knows nothing but chaos.
The film received negative reviews from critics, but it was nevertheless a box office success,
grossing $72.2 million worldwide against a production budget of $11 million.
Problem Child was followed by two sequels, Problem Child 2 (1991) and the made for TV
Problem Child 3: Junior in Love (1995) as well as an animated series.
The film explores themes of nurse, parent child
relationship, dark comedy, ice hockey, spoiled child.
The tone is lighthearted and dark.